const myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "In which game, every assassinated person is a real one with accurate death date and place?",
        answers: {
            a: "Dishonored",
            b: "Assassins's Creed",
            c: "Hitman",
            d: "Call of Duty"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which year the PS4 was released?",
        answers: {
            a: "2013",
            b: "2014",
            c: "2016",
            d: "2012"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Who developed Destiny 2?",
        answers: {
            a: "Ubisoft",
            b: "Santa Monica Studios",
            c: "EA Games",
            d: "Bungie"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Resident Evil 7 is released in which year?",
        answers: {
            a: "2018",
            b: "2014",
            c: "2017",
            d: "2016"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the primary protagonist of the God of War Series?",
        answers: {
            a: "Thor",
            b: "Kratos",
            c: "Aterus",
            d: "Zues"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Who are the original creators of Rachet & Clank?",
        answers: {
            a: "Insomniac Games",
            b: "Bungie",
            c: "Ubisoft",
            d: "Santa Monica Studios"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "In the Halo series, what is the name of the race of aliens humans refer to as Grunts?",
        answers: {
            a: "Salamander",
            b: "Voldermort",
            c: "Unggoy",
            d: "Mark Tyson"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What time traveling device appears in Assassinâ€™s Creed?",
        answers: {
            a: "Time sphere",
            b: "Animus",
            c: "Cosmic treadmill",
            d: "Epoch"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first video game console?",
        answers: {
            a: "Magnavox Odyssey",
            b: "Atari 2600",
            c: "Intellivision",
            d: "Sega SG-100"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Grand Theft Auto game was the first to offer playable female characters?",
        answers: {
            a: "Grand Theft Auto Online",
            b: "Grand Theft Auto 4: The Ballad of Gay Tony",
            c: "Grand Theft Auto",
            d: "None of the above"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    }
];